Radio CPR PUNK001
People's Archive, MLK Library
Radio CPR Collection
1997-2008
People's Archive, MLK Library
Radio CPR (Radio station: Washington, D.C.)
PUNK001
7 Boxes
Punk rock music
- Series 1
  - Stand for our Neighbors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Prometheus, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Radio/Media Clippings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MBC Letters Received, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Norton Letter - MBC Support, 8/2/1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Letter from Eleanor Holmes Norton to The Honorable William E. Kennard
  - MBC Petitions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MBC Incorporation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    MBC Articles of Incorporation, Bylaws, and Waiver of Notice of Organization Meeting of Directors
  - Micropower Showdown - 1998, 10/1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - MBC Frequency Search, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - MBC Application, 6/5/2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - FCC Knock!, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - How to start a pirate station!, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CPR, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Technical, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Article - Micropower Broadcasting: A Technical Primer
  - CPR Packets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Radio CPR, 97.5 FM: Our mission and history
  - Microradio Clippings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Radio in the News, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - WGTB, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Black Liberation Radio, 02/1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Equipment, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Reception Tips, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Spectrum, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pro-Pirate Resolutions, 10/18/1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    City of Grover Beach, California Proclamation of the City Council of the City of Grover Beach Recognizing Excellent Radio 88.9 FM
  - MBC Policies, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - MBC Training, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - MBC Comments, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Incorporation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Bylaws
  - MBC Letterhead, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - MBC Ideas/Photos, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Station Program Guides, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - German Free Radio, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Micro Radio Legal, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Int'l Free Radio/Other, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - MBC Zines, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Phone List, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, February 2001 - August 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, August 2001 - October 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, November 2001 - December 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, January 2002 - April 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, April 2002 - August 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, September 2002 - December 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, February 2004 - April 2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, May 2004 - June 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, July 2004 - September 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, October 2004 - December 2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Radio CPR 97.5 FM Traffic/Program Log, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Certificates of Achievement for Radio Broadcasting/Photographs/Move Pa'lante Magazine, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mount Pleasant Broadcasting Club Petitions/Nov 2004 Program Calendar (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Transistor Diagrams, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - CPR Storybooth, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Understanding Radio Handouts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - CPR Contact Lists Feb 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Benefit Shows, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cabaret Del Barrio, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Christmas Eve Sacred Heart Dinners, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - DJ Show Fliers, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Economic Human Rights Campaign/Cheri Honkala, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - First Broadcast, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lamont Street Halloween, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - MBC, etc., Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mount Pleasant Festival - Youth Stage, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photos of DJs, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Protests, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Stand for our Neighbors, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - YARG Youth Radio, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)